{
  "a1": "Yes.  The work we did during the 2018 Legislative Session to set aside gaming revenue should be used to fund the reforms identified by the commission.",
  "a10": "Ensure that we balance providing treatment with any criminal sanctions.",
  "a11": "Income inequality  can be addressed through increasing access to education and providing jobs with a living wage.",
  "a12": "yes",
  "a2": "It is very difficult to balance between roads and transit.  We need to increase funding so we have adequate resources to meet our transportation needs.",
  "a3": "In theory I am not opposed but I think the language has to be well drafted.",
  "a4": "Step up our stormwater regulations.",
  "a5": "We need to work towards creating a single payer system.",
  "a6": "Funding for rehabilitation programs and expansion of Safe Streets.",
  "a7": "We have taken great strides to encourage business growth.",
  "a8": "Yes",
  "a9": "yes",
  "age": 38,
  "background": "I am an attorney by trade and training.",
  "directory": "content/state-senate/district-25",
  "district": 25,
  "dob": "12/26/1979",
  "education": "Hampton University, BA  Political Science University of Yeshiva, Cardozo School of Law",
  "filename": "angela-m-angel.md",
  "full-name": "Angela M. Angel",
  "jurisdiction": "Prince George's County",
  "last-name": "Angel",
  "party": "Democrat",
  "q1": "Do you support the findings of the Commission on Innovation and Excellence in Education? Are you committed to funding associated reforms, and if so, how?",
  "q10": "What strategy would you adopt to address the opioid addiction and overdose crisis?",
  "q11": "What if anything should the state do to address income inequality?",
  "q12": "Do the state’s Public Information Act and open meetings laws adequately ensure Marylanders’ ability to exercise oversight of the government?",
  "q2": "Is Maryland’s transportation spending appropriately balanced between roads and transit? Does the state have the resources to meet its transportation needs? With the cancellation of the Red Line and the advent of BaltimoreLink, is the Baltimore region adequately served by transit?",
  "q3": "Do you support the legalization of recreational marijuana?",
  "q4": "At a time when the federal government’s commitment to Chesapeake Bay restoration is questionable, what new steps should Maryland take to protect this resource?",
  "q5": "What steps should Maryland take to ensure the broadest possible access to affordable health care?",
  "q6": "What role should the state play in helping Baltimore address violent crime?",
  "q7": "How would you characterize Maryland’s business climate? What can the state do to foster the creation of more family-supporting jobs?",
  "q8": "Do you support the creation of a non-partisan, independent body to draw legislative and congressional district maps after each census?",
  "q9": "Does the Law Enforcement Officers Bill of Rights adequately balance protections for police and the public? Should it be changed, and if so, how?",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Do you support the findings of the Commission on Innovation and Excellence in Education? Are you committed to funding associated reforms, and if so, how?",
      "answer": "Yes.  The work we did during the 2018 Legislative Session to set aside gaming revenue should be used to fund the reforms identified by the commission.",
      "shortname": "Kirwan"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is Maryland’s transportation spending appropriately balanced between roads and transit? Does the state have the resources to meet its transportation needs? With the cancellation of the Red Line and the advent of BaltimoreLink, is the Baltimore region adequately served by transit?",
      "answer": "It is very difficult to balance between roads and transit.  We need to increase funding so we have adequate resources to meet our transportation needs.",
      "shortname": "Transportation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you support the legalization of recreational marijuana?",
      "answer": "In theory I am not opposed but I think the language has to be well drafted.",
      "shortname": "Marijuana"
    },
    {
      "question": "At a time when the federal government’s commitment to Chesapeake Bay restoration is questionable, what new steps should Maryland take to protect this resource?",
      "answer": "Step up our stormwater regulations.",
      "shortname": "Chesapeake Bay"
    },
    {
      "question": "What steps should Maryland take to ensure the broadest possible access to affordable health care?",
      "answer": "We need to work towards creating a single payer system.",
      "shortname": "Health Care"
    },
    {
      "question": "What role should the state play in helping Baltimore address violent crime?",
      "answer": "Funding for rehabilitation programs and expansion of Safe Streets.",
      "shortname": "Crime"
    },
    {
      "question": "How would you characterize Maryland’s business climate? What can the state do to foster the creation of more family-supporting jobs?",
      "answer": "We have taken great strides to encourage business growth.",
      "shortname": "Business Climate"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you support the creation of a non-partisan, independent body to draw legislative and congressional district maps after each census?",
      "answer": "Yes",
      "shortname": "Redistricting"
    },
    {
      "question": "Does the Law Enforcement Officers Bill of Rights adequately balance protections for police and the public? Should it be changed, and if so, how?",
      "answer": "yes",
      "shortname": "LEOBR"
    },
    {
      "question": "What strategy would you adopt to address the opioid addiction and overdose crisis?",
      "answer": "Ensure that we balance providing treatment with any criminal sanctions.",
      "shortname": "Opioids"
    },
    {
      "question": "What if anything should the state do to address income inequality?",
      "answer": "Income inequality  can be addressed through increasing access to education and providing jobs with a living wage.",
      "shortname": "Income inequality"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do the state’s Public Information Act and open meetings laws adequately ensure Marylanders’ ability to exercise oversight of the government?",
      "answer": "yes",
      "shortname": "Transparency"
    }
  ],
  "race": "state-senate",
  "residence": "Anne Arundel County",
  "sn1": "Kirwan",
  "sn10": "Opioids",
  "sn11": "Income inequality",
  "sn12": "Transparency",
  "sn2": "Transportation",
  "sn3": "Marijuana",
  "sn4": "Chesapeake Bay",
  "sn5": "Health Care",
  "sn6": "Crime",
  "sn7": "Business Climate",
  "sn8": "Redistricting",
  "sn9": "LEOBR",
  "social-fb": "mdadvocateangel",
  "social-tw": "mdadvocateangel",
  "survey-response": true,
  "title": "Angela M. Angel",
  "web": "http://www.advocateangel.com"
}
